STEFAN DRAGIĆEVIĆ

Sombor, Serbia +381 63 765 01 01 dragicevic.a.stefan@gmail.com https://dragicevics.github.io/portfolio-website/

ABOUT

Experienced in various roles, I bring a strong work ethic and a desire to continually learn. I'm an effective communicator who values teamwork and respects others. Committed to health and productivity, I use technology to achieve goals efficiently.

JOB SPECIFIC SKILLS

React JavaScript TypeScript HTML & CSS

Git Vite / Webpack Responsive design SEO

Jest English language Problem solver Polite and respectful

EDUCATION

Military Grammar School

2010 - 2014

Belgrade, Serbia

General stream high school with a boarding program

WORK EXPERIENCE

Warehouse Manager

08/2016 - 03/2023

Somboled d.o.o., Sombor

- Working with WMS and SAP systems
- Organizing tasks on a daily basis
- Preparing necessary documentation (delivery notes, cargo manifests, invoices, etc.)
- Adjusting equipment for packers and forklift operators for further work

OTHER

IT Academy 2016 -2017

Belgrade, Serbia

PHP web programming course